

PLATFORMS

in LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/svetosla v-yordanov003/

GitHub

https://github.com/yordanov03

Web Card

https://yordanov03.github.io/

LANGUAGES

English

German ••••

SKILLS

C# · SQL · Javascript · Typescript ·

HTML5 · CSS · Mongodb · .NetCore ·

ASP.NET · .NetFramework · Angular · Git ·

Azure · Docker · Kubernetes · CI/CD ·

Microservices · Bitbucket · Redux · Rxjs

PROJECTS

Wohngeld Go

Link

 State projects aimed at providing financial aid for housing rentals

NOTABLE CERTIFICATION

Azure Developer Associate

Cloud Solutions Developer AZ-204

Azure Cosmos DB Developer

Microsoft DP420 Certificate

Azure Fundamentals

Microsoft certified AZ-900

REFERENCE LETTERS

Credit Suisse AG

thinfabrics Gmbh

Hewlett Packard Enterprise

DXC technology

Svetoslav Yordanov

MicrosoftDeveloper Associate

+4179 507 3951 @ svetoslav.yordanov.003@gmail.com

Zurich, Switzerland

SUMMARY

Passionate Software Engineer with several years of experience in developing web applications and backend systems. Skilled at writing clear, concise code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies. Able to work independently of remote locations or in office environments as needed by the company.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer

2023 - Present

Swisscom AG

- Spearhead the development of scalable applications, delivering efficient solutions that enhance corporate security, network overview and business functionality.
- Design and implement Network Access Control (NAC) solutions, utilizing real-time state management tools to enhance system monitoring, security, and performance across diverse IT environments.
- Proactively manage potential security vulnerabilities through layered security protocols within the network infrastructure, ensuring top-tier security standards

Full Stack Developer

2022 - 2022

Credit Suisse AG

- Creation of web tools with .NetCore, Angular and SQL of significant matter for the decision-making for future investments
- Proactively involved in the full lifecycle of tools for process automation
- Developing optimizations and cost-effectiveness via creating custom-tailored tools according to the needs of the business
- Cloud application development and migration

Full Stack Developer

2021 - 2022

Freelancer

- Design, implementation and deployment of tools as per customer specifications
- Monolith or microservices architecture based in cloud environment
- Integration of third party applications (Dynatrace, Keypay, Mailchimp etc.)
- Performing root cause analysis to identify bugs and roll out fixes to production

Software Developer

2020 - 2021

thinfabrics Gmbh - Bulpros consulting

- Lead Developer, participating actively decision-making concerning tech stack and deployment
- Developing new features and integration with existing services for state project, aimed at providing financial aid for housing commodities
- Refactor legacy code and update internal customer framework
- Due to timely project completion, the development of 7 more projects was entrusted to us by the same costumer

EDUCATION

Web developer 2017 - 2019

Software university

Master's degree in Marketing and 2013 - 2015 communications

University of National and World Economy

Bachelor in International Relations 2008 - 2012

University of National and World Economy